married in like 2 days or something? I
am, indeed, yeah.
Big week for the kid, huh?
>> [laughter]
>> All right, John.
Congrats, Jeremy. Um, what does this
mean to you that they would do this for
you? Uh, it's amazing, John. First of
all, good to see you, brother. Um,
but uh, it's amazing, man. Anytime, you
know, like I said, value is the most
important thing in the NFL. Um, and for
me to feel that value again, you know,
and just that appreciation from the guys
in this building, not only my teammates,
but the staff. Um, it's a blessing. I
don't take it for granted. Um, I know
how my career started and what it took
to get to this point, so
any chance is a, you know, is just
something I'm thankful for.
I'm also curious, too. A lot of moves on
that defense this offseason. Just with
some of the players they brought in,
what have you thought about what the
approach they've taken defensively this
offseason?
Uh, aggressive, man. I I just was
talking to uh, AP and I was just telling
him like, you know, obviously last year
wasn't enough and it wasn't good enough.
And even the year before wasn't good
enough, either, because the ultimate
goal wasn't done. So,
um,
we're not trying to make the same same
mistakes twice, you know? So, like, any
chance that we can get to get better,
um, to put ourselves in the best
position to win, we're going to do that.
So, I mean, yeah, the proof is in the
what we've done, right? I've got a
chance to talk to
Nick and um,
couple guys, and so uh, it's exciting,
man. Like, I'm ready to get on board
with these guys and get to rolling and
uh, start putting the pieces together so
we can be playing football in February.
Mention and congrats on all on all
fronts. Appreciate that, my boy.
Nicky.
Um, congrats on a lot of things. Um,
just uh, having been through everything
with this organization, um, what does it
mean to you to get get another extension
with them? I Like I said, I mean,
knowing how my career started, I was a
undrafted eighth-round pick, you know?
Um,
and I bounced around on the practice
squad and up and down for, you know, the
better part, I guess you could say, of
my good years in the league, um, when I
was younger.
And, you know, getting the opportunity
in that fifth year and becoming all-pro
and a pro bowler and never looking back
and now, you know, I'm on
I guess my third contract, where in
reality, like, that seemed like a
distant thought at the time. But, you
know, the persistence and the
just the steadiness of how I approached
every day and every year, um,
it's amazing, man. It just goes to show,
man, like,
it does not matter what people believe
about you or what people think about you
or what stats or numbers or any of that
stuff says about you, right? Like, the
belief starts with you and how you put
your best foot forward every day is
where you get to where you want to go.
None of those other things matter. And
so, um, if anybody needed a testament to
it, you can just look at me cuz I I'm
living proof that uh, it can be done.
So, I'm just grateful. I'm thankful, um,
for every
hard part of life that I've experienced,
every downfall, every loss. Um, it all
shaped me
and made me who I am today. And so, I
can sit here in front of you guys 2 days
before my wedding and uh,
talk about this.
And have you had a chance to to meet
with Durante Jones yet? And if so, what
are your early impressions? Uh, it was
very brief. Um, obviously there was a
lot going on and it's a tight ship right
now. [laughter]
I'm pretty much in and out, but um,
yeah, I got to talk to him a little bit,
but, you know, I think it's pretty it's
funny, you know, uh,
I've kind of learned in my life that
you can kind of get a jump on somebody
in the first reaction of like meeting
them, right? First impressions mean a
lot. Um, he's a very direct person. You
know, he's very stern and he's very, you
know, I can tell he's a very honest man.
Um,
but I can also tell that he's here to
win. And uh, you know, he's here to
figure out how to put people in the best
positions to win. Um, and you know,
watching some of y'all's pressures and
stuff and watching his pressure when he
first got here,
uh, he's so detailed in how he speaks
about the game and also like how he has
a plan for each player.
Um, I think that's kind of cool. You
know, you don't really hear about that a
lot of, you know, how it's broken down
into segments of how
they can teach it or or or instruct it
in a way that each guy understands it so
it best suits the player. Um, I think
that's a amazing quality that not a lot
of people have. So, yeah, I've been
paying attention to y'all just as much.
So, uh,
yeah, I'm uh, I'm excited to get to work
with him, man. And um, it's exciting
times here. I will say that.
David.
Congrats, Jeremy, on on everything, man.
Just just continue to stay blessed, bro.
I'm happy for you. Appreciate that,
brother.
Um, I don't think Candy's going to be
able to make it. She just kind of want
to follow She has Deonna here. Question
about persevering through adversity and
coming out on the other side better. I
know you've had a lot of experience with
that as well. Obviously, resiliency is a
big topic right now just across the
league
because of, unfortunately, what
happened, but also just people wanting
to kind of follow up on that. So, if you
could give a message to to a player, you
know, who's who's been in in your
position before and going to go through
their own kind of thing about resiliency
and and maybe feeling left behind
sometimes and forgotten, what would that
message be? Uh,
I think it's pretty simple, right? Um,
the turtle wins the race. I say that all
the time. But uh,
embrace being the turtle. I think so
much we get caught up in being the lion
or the or the the cheetah and wanting to
get there fast, but uh,
you know, fast isn't always good. Um,
so sometimes I think we we miss the the
lessons and the blessings that come with
the race and the marathon of it. Um, so
embrace it. Um, it's going to be some
tough days. It's going to be some
uncomfortable days. It's going to be
some days you have doubt. Um, you human.
Everybody is. We all have those moments
in life where we don't quite know if
we're good enough to be where we are, to
do what we do.
Um, but my message to you is is is
simple that uh, you are enough. You have
enough. Um, you have what it takes.
The belief starts with you and it ends
with you. And anywhere that you want to
go in life, no matter what profession,
job, title you have,
um,
there's always more out there for you.
Um, so don't limit yourself or put
yourself in a box because other people
have.
Um,
you kind of dictate your own fate. So,
yeah.
No, that's awesome, man. Um, a very hard
gear shift. I don't want to get too deep
into your personal life, um, but given
that your officiant also is going to be
aware that you have a new contract, are
you concerned he's going to up the rate
at all for for officiating your wedding?
Nah, man. I uh,
uh, it's open bar, so I picked up the
tab on my guy.
Um,
nah, man, but I I'm uh,
I'm so excited to have him a part of my
wedding, man. He's been a such a such a
huge part of my life.
He changed my life. I mean,
one conversation he had changed my life,
um, from that point forward.
So, um, to have him a part of the
biggest day of my life is uh, something
that I uh, will always cherish and
remember. So, I'll I'll let y'all know
who cried more, him or me, but I
I'll bet the house that it's him.
Appreciate it, Jeremy. Thank you. No
problem, brother. Thank you.
Donna.
Hey, Jeremy. Uh, welcome. Uh, um, glad
that you got that extension. And I love
the fact that you said the turtle wins
the race. That's that's pretty good.
But, could you talk about You said
something about belief. Uh, obviously,
the Commanders believed in you with this
extension. But, could you talk about
your belief in yourself?
Uh, yeah, I mean, it's it's I mean, it's
kind of
Belief comes through trial and error.
Belief comes through failing. Belief
also comes through winning, right?
Um,
when you fall, I think the greatest
lesson of falling is learning to pick
yourself back up again. Um, and getting
back to the drawing board. So, falling
and failing actually was what made me
have belief in myself because once I got
back to where I needed to go, right?
Once I was cut and worked myself back
and cut again and cut again and worked
myself back and then you finally break a
roster, right? That's where belief
starts to to to come in. And then when
you tear your ACL on a contract year
after going all-pro,
you fall down again with a new staff
coming in and you have no idea what to
expect or if they're going to want you
or whatever it may be. And then you
build yourself back up again to to come
back and play in 6, 7 months. Um,
that's where belief is forged. Belief is
forged every day. It's forged in the
things that people don't see, right? The
thing how you talk to yourself, how you
approach each day, what you tell
yourself. Um,
the mind is a powerful muscle, man.
Like, it's the most powerful muscle in
the body. The body is going to do
whatever the mind tells it to. Um, and
so,
it was just for me, it was just the
constant reassurance of myself. Like,
yeah, it sucks right now. Yeah, I'm not
where I want to be, but I'mma get there.
I have my goals written down. In 2019, I
told the world I was going to be a pro
bowler and I was a practice squad guy.
And then you fast forward down the road
and I became a pro bowler.
Um, and so, like, I just told myself
that. I I trained my mind to think that
and then the body followed. And so, you
know, it's it's kind of that's that's
the recipe, honestly.
And and could you talk a little bit
about leadership because you are a
leader on this team. And and what that
means to you as far as leading by
example? Um, it means the world to me
because I think the qualities of a great
leader is first you have to know how to
follow. Um, and I spent the early parts
of my career following some really great
vets that I kind of learned how to be a
pro from.
And so, watching those guys be ultimate
pros and ultimate competitors, it helped
me be able to be a leader in my own way.
And my way is a connector, right? Like,
I connect with people from all
backgrounds, places. Don't care what
color you are, don't care where you're
from. Like, I'm in the business of
trying to make the next man or person
next to me a little bit better or make
their day a little bit better than it
was yesterday.
Um,
and so, that's just honestly it's just
spending time, taking time out of your
day to get to know the person,
not the the player or the the media or
the, you know, the coach the actual
person of it. Um and that's what makes
me me. That's what has always made me
me. That was a
trait that my mom gave me. So, um
I think leadership best is best
described as um
how you connect with people and how you
can make people believe in themselves.
So,
Congrats and well deserved.
>> Thank you. Appreciate that.
Ben.
Hey Jeremy, congrats
for everything. Thank you. Thank you.
Obviously
like you just said you only just talked
to Durantae briefly, but in broad
strokes based on what we think this new
defense could look like, what's does
anything change for the safeties based
on this group versus this system versus
what you were just in? Nah, from from
the scope that I've gotten from things
like he likes violence and we have a lot
of violent people in that room. Um I
think schematically obviously it'll be a
little different. We'll run different um
things on the back end. Um
From what I've seen on tape, they're a
lot of two shell and they make the two
shell look a lot like single high or
vice versa. They roll in and out of
coverages.
Um but I don't think it'll be very much
different. Football's football, right? I
tell y'all this all the time. You run
cover three, you run cover four, you run
cover two. Everybody runs same thing.
They just make it look different. Um so,
the game is going to be the game. I
think it's just how the game looks from
that lens of the quarterback is going to
be played a little different, which is
the biggest part of the game, honestly.
And to end on a silly somewhat note. So,
how involved were you in the wedding
planning? Were you like all in or you
just stay back? Uh man, listen here,
man. Happy wife, happy life, right? I
cut the checkbook and I said, "Baby, you
get whatever you want." Man.
>> [laughter]
[snorts]
>> Smart man, congrats. Thank you, brother.
Appreciate it.
Blake.
Welcome back, my guy. Good to see you,
man.
>> Appreciate that, brother.
When you
you know, look at just your career as a
whole and where you've come from and
maybe even some of the promises in
previous groups, to see the love that
you're getting now from this, you know,
organization, how special is that for
you?
Uh indescribable, brother.
Um
Uh you know, it's the first time in my
career where I've just like really felt
wanted by an entire organization. Top
down, right? Like
not just this year, obviously, but like
coming off my ACL, right? Like they
could have went any direction. They
could have went any route, right? Like
they don't know me.
I'm Yes, I had a great year before, but
like I hurt my knee and you never know
how guys are going to come back.
So, for them to have just that
that patience with me, but also just
like that cuz this is like, "Hey, like
you're our guy."
Like we love you. We love what you bring
to the table. We love who you are as a
person, as a player. Um we want you a
part of this.
Um yeah, man. I mean, you can't ask for
nothing more. Like coming from where I
came from and how I had to
had to get it out of mud, really. Like
all I asked all I wanted was just for to
feel wanted and appreciated for, you
know, the things that I do. Like I mean,
you guys all know like
I live and die with this, right? Like I
I lay it on the line every week and it's
not just for me, right? It's not just
for my livelihood, but it's for
everybody else, right? I want everybody
else around me
to succeed and to win because I know how
hard it is to win in this business or in
life in general.
So,
um
to feel that recognition and that
appreciation for, you know, the things
that I do, man, it cuz it can get swept
under the rug, right?
Special teams as a whole, right? The
world doesn't look at it as a big thing,
but I mean, those of us that are in it
or a part of it know understand that
like it all plays a role. It all has a
a factor in the game. It can win or lose
games.
Um
and so, for that to be, you know, a
pivotal thing here and how much they
stress it and how much they want dudes
out there and for me to be considered
one of those dudes, I'm a
I'm grateful, man.
I'm I'm I'm thankful.
And then finally, you know, just the the
success that you guys had 2 years ago
and then last year not, you know,
carrying that over with injuries and
things of that nature, how excited are
are you to to to see all the new pieces
coming into the building and and and the
fact that, you know, last year even that
the team never turned their back on each
other. The locker room was still tight.
How excited are you for this season? Uh
well, first off, I'm excited cuz
uh as a competitor,
I still got a terrible taste in my mouth
from that season. Like that was
uh
that was rough. It was tough. Um
and if you love competing and you love
winning, like nobody's trying to go out
like that. And our whole locker room as
a whole was not trying to go out like
that, you know? So, like
I'm just eager to play football again
because
I've been thinking about that since it
ended, to be honest. So, um
The guys are the guys in there, man.
Like we all rock with each other. We all
love each other.
And we all want to see each other do
well, right? Like it's
it's a special group of men in there.
Special group of dudes. And so, like the
cool part about it is we got so many
pieces that are back. We just piggyback
off of what we kind of had in as far as
like the relationships. Um
But at the same time, because we got so
many people back, the standard got to
grow. We need more out of everybody
because whatever we did last year wasn't
good enough. And whatever we did the
year before wasn't good enough either
cuz we didn't win it. So,
um
It's it's a it's a awesome feeling
because now you get to amplify
expectations amongst each other because
you know each other. And I think that's
what great teams do, right? Like if my
brother knows I want the best for him,
then if I get on to him, then he not
going to take it personal. He
understands that this is what's going to
make him and us better.
All right, congrats and you know a lot
of people are pulling for you.
Appreciate that, boss man.
All right. Go ahead, Nikki. You're last
one. I just want to know how did you ask
Truss to officiate your wedding? Like
how did that go down? I called him on
FaceTime and I was like, "Listen,
brother, like you've been a big part of
my life.
I would like you to be a part the
biggest part of my life and officiate my
wedding, man." And he was ecstatic and
he was excited and I was excited and my
lady was excited. Um sad that the bow
man and the kiddos can't come. It's a no
kids only this grown folks thing over
here.
But uh
I uh I'm looking forward to seeing them.
That's family right there, man. Like
blood don't make you family.
Uh
relationships and and and and people do
and how they treat you. And that is that
is my family right there. And I live and
die about them and I'm just so excited
to get to share the big day with them.
Will there will there be video of the
said officiation?
>> Oh, yeah, for sure. I Listen, y'all will
see. I'll get all the video and photos
out to y'all for sure. No doubt.
All right, congrats, Jeremy. Appreciate
y'all. Thank y'all. Congrats, Jeremy.
Congrats.
I got top five uh